[
    {
        "cell_ids": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13],
        "question": "What is the average quantity of products purchased in a transaction?",
       "answer": "The notebook does not explicitly compute the average quantity of products purchased per transaction, but it calculates and presents the mean quantity, which is 11.834 in cell 16.",
       "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
     {
        "cell_ids": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
             13
        ],
        "question": "What are the most frequently purchased items in France based on the provided data?",
        "answer": "The notebook uses a different dataset for mlxtend package which is for e-commerce store and not for France region specifically, and it shows coffee as most popular in cell 14.",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
   {
        "cell_ids": [
          1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13
        ],
      "question": "What is the number of unique transactions in the dataset?",
       "answer":"The notebook removes cancelled transactions but doesn't calculate or show the number of unique transactions explicitly. It is derived based on the pivot table.",
         "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
   {
        "cell_ids": [37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42],
        "question": "What is the most frequent itemset identified by the Apriori algorithm with a minimum support of 0.07, using the mlxtend package?",
        "answer": "Based on cell 40, the frequent itemset(s) are shown with their respective support values. However, it is mentioned that the function has a default minimum support of 0.01, but not that any specific itemset is the most frequent.",
        "task":"Association Rule Mining",
        "skill": "Apriori Algorithm"
   },
   {
      "cell_ids": [
        37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42
      ],
        "question":"What is the highest lift value among the association rules generated from the mlxtend output?",
      "answer": "Based on the code in cell 42, the highest lift value is 21.556122 associated with (SET/6 RED SPOTTY PAPER PLATES), and (SET/6 RED SPOTTY PAPER CUPS) itemsets.",
        "task": "Association Rule Mining",
         "skill": "Apriori Algorithm"
    },
    {
      "cell_ids":[
         37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42
        ],
      "question": "What is the item that has highest confidence when someone buyes toast?",
      "answer": "The notebook does not have toast as an item from the generated rules.",
       "task":"Association Rule Mining",
      "skill":"Apriori Algorithm"
    },
{
        "cell_ids": [
            45,
            46,
            47,
            48,
            49
        ],
        "question": "If a customer buys product with id 22326, what are the top 3 product recommendations based on the notebook's analysis?",
       "answer":"Based on the function in cell 49 and the output of cell 51, the top 3 product recommendations for a customer who buys item 22326 are: (22328, 'ROUND SNACK BOXES SET OF 4 FRUITS '), (22554, 'PLASTERS IN TIN WOODLAND ANIMALS'), and (22629, 'SPACEBOY LUNCH BOX ').",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Apriori Algorithm"
   },
  {
        "cell_ids": [
            45, 46, 47, 48, 49
        ],
        "question": "If a customer buys product with id 22725, what are the top 3 product recommendations based on the notebook's analysis?",
       "answer": "Based on the output of the function in cell 52, the top 3 product recommendations for item id '22725' are: (22727, 'ALARM CLOCK BAKELIKE RED '), (22326, 'ROUND SNACK BOXES SET OF4 WOODLAND '), and (22728, 'ALARM CLOCK BAKELIKE PINK').",
       "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Apriori Algorithm"
  },
    {
      "cell_ids":[
        45, 46, 47, 48, 49
       ],
        "question": "If a customer buys product with id 22809, what are the product recommendations based on the notebook's analysis?",
      "answer": "The notebook output indicates that \"There is no product can be recommended!\" for item id 22809 in cell 53.",
       "task":"Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Apriori Algorithm"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            45, 46, 47, 48, 49
        ],
        "question":"If a customer buys product with id 2256523, is it a valid id based on the notebook analysis?",
         "answer": "The notebook output indicates that \"Invalid Product Id, try again!\" for product id 2256523 in cell 54",
        "task": "Recommendation Systems",
         "skill":"Apriori Algorithm"
    }
]